topseos.in 2015-06-08

# topseos Privacy Policy

Updated: Wednesday, September 5, 2012

## NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

We may update this Privacy Agreement from time to time as our services change and expand.

## THIS SITE CONTAINS LINKS TO OTHER SITES

topseos.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the Content of any other Web sites to which the Site links to or which link to the Site. By clicking on a link, logo, or other item, please note that You may no longer be on the topseos.com Site.

## INFORMATION WE GATHER

If You register to buy or sell services using topseos.com, We collect and store information that specifically identifies You or Your account (“Personally Identifiable Information”).

## YOUR PUBLIC PROFILE

As part of registration, We collect information which is used to generate a Company Profile of service providers. After subscribing, You must create a Profile, and in order to create a Profile, You will be required to provide some information about Your company or business. If You decide to offer a service, potential buyers will look to your Company Profile to help them decide whether to make an offer on your service or not.

## HOW WE USE INFORMATION

## REGISTRATION INFORMATION

We use Personally Identifiable Information for our own internal purposes including contacting You via email to inform You about updates to our services and providing You with information relating to e-commerce transactions that You conduct on the Site. We reserve the right to disclose your information as required by law. We may additionally provide You with newsletters via email.

## HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION

We collect personal information about You as peruse of our Site, interact with our customer service representatives, complete online order forms or information request sheets, and provide your information to our sales agents. We may use cookies and pixel tags to track Your usage of our websites. We also use online order forms and information request sheets to obtain information from You necessary to process your orders and provide You with requested information.

## EMAIL TRANSMISSIONS

We may send email transmissions to our users about various products and services being offered. We may also send requests to users in regards to updating their profiles or providing more complete information about their company. In addition, we may send out promotional messages on behalf of our Affiliates regarding their products and services.

All Users, unless otherwise unsubscribed from further email transmissions, will receive the promotional and transactional messages via the email address which they used when registering their company profile. In addition, users which opt-in to our email notification system will also be transmitted promotional messages unless they opt-out of communication. e-ventures Worldwide, LLC provides users with a way to opt-out of communication in accordance with the CAN-SPAM Act via a link provided at the bottom of email transmissions in which the user can send a response to the email to be removed from the email list.

For all opt-out requests, please allow three to five business days for your email to be removed from our system. For requests sent via mail or telephone, please allow additional time for the message to be delivered in order for the opt-out request to be handled.

## SECURITY MEASURES

We have created and implemented a variety of encryption and security technologies and procedures to protect information stored in our systems for from unauthorized access. Further, we maintain procedural safeguards that restrict access to your personal and private Customer Information to topseos.com employees who need to know your Customer Information in order to provide the services that you request from time to time.

## ACCESS TO INFORMATION

In the event that you have any concerns or inquiries about the Customer Information we have collected, or to access your information, please e-mail us at info@topseos.com or write to e-ventures Worldwide, LLC, Privacy Department, 2338 Immokalee Rd, Suite 404, Naples, FL 34110-1445. We may require the payment of a minimal administrative fee for accessing or copying your information, but will inform you of the anticipated charges and confirm that you want us to proceed before processing your request. If you believe that the Customer Information about you that we have collected is incomplete or inaccurate, we will correct the information upon verification of the omission or error and that the person requesting the change is the person about whom the Customer Information relates.

## LEGAL DISCLAIMER

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website.
